https://ghostvillage.com/about/privacy-statement/

PRIVACY STATEMENT
Privacy StatementGhostvillage.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Ghostvillage.com
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help identify where our users are coming from, and to profile where our marketing efforts are working best.
Personal Information
This Web site does collect personal information that is voluntarily provided by its users. At times, Ghostvillage.com may contact its members with business offerings. However, we do not share any personal information with any third parties.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Ghostvillage.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: info@ghostvillage.com
Advanced Search
Check out Jeff Belanger's Emmy-nominated TV series: New England Legends -- as seen on PBS!
Don’t miss the following events and lectures:
VIRTUAL Creepy Christmas with Jeff Belanger at the Manchester City Library
© 1999-2020 Ghostvillage.com, All Rights Reserved.
